#### Miguel HD Younger

Dallas, PA 18612 570-709-8577 miguel.younger@gmail.com

I have over 24 years of experience in online service and e-commerce industries. My early roles were in design, conversion rate optimization and management while my more recent roles focused on operations, product & project management. I have applied continuous improvement methods in all of our operations.



#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Enspire for Enterprise, Remote

Vice President, Program Development Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

- Note: Web for Enterprise division of Web.com was acquired by <u>Constellation</u> <u>Software</u> in February 2020.
- Lead the implementation team to onboard our clients and deliver our projects on time, on budget and as expected.
- Managed vendor relations and contract negotiations.
- Assisted with transition of personnel and processes into our new organization.

### Web.com, Hazleton, PA

Vice President, Product Delivery Oct 2013 - Feb 2020

- Lead the legacy e-commerce team's daily operations and new product development.
- Managed department and role change as our legacy e-commerce team became
  part of a targeted enterprise Agency team that served clients with unique
  technology needs. My focus transitioned to Project management leadership
  within the team.
- Managed department change as our Agency team merged with the Web for Enterprise division that served national franchise brands.

### Vice President, Operations, Solid Cactus Apr 2009 - Oct 2013

- Note: Solid Cactus, Inc. was acquired by Web.com in April 2009.
- Responsible for ongoing e-commerce operations, special projects and ultimately assimilating legacy Solid Cactus brands to Web.com.
- Manage local (Hazleton, PA) and remote (Jacksonville, FL) teams
   (e-commerce websites, online marketing, SaaS & call center services.)
- Worked with each department's directors to meet continuous improvement and client service objectives.
- Hold quarterly all-hands meetings with staff to review our division's state of business.

# Solid Cactus, Inc., Wilkes-Barre, PA

Vice President, Operations Mar 2008 - Apr 2009

- Responsible for ongoing operations of the e-commerce website, online marketing, SaaS, call center and support teams.
- Work closely with each department director to meet monthly objectives.

# General Manager of Store Development Dec 2006 - Mar 2008

• Managed all e-commerce website teams: account management, project management, creative and development.

Responsible for meeting monthly financial targets and project metrics.

### Director of Project Management Aug 2005 - Dec 2006

- Defined project management processes and metrics to support our rapid growth.
- Managed e-commerce projects from sales to launch and offered post launch support.

### Account Management Jan 2005 - Aug 2005

- Managed a book of e-commerce clients, their projects, handled support, and performed upsells.
- Liaison between creative, development and clients.



Self Employed Oct 2002 - Jan 2005

- Operated as a single creative consultant and design production house.
- Performed all estimates, sales, billing, project management, design and development of client websites.

# Randall Design, Inc.

MHDY.com

Art Director Aug 1997 - Oct 2002

 Co-Art Director of our designers, met with clients, and executed website (design & development) work as needed.

Graphic Designer Dec 1996 - Aug 1997

• Designed print catalogs and performed studio product photography.

### **SKILLS**

- MS Office Excel, Word, and PPT
- General HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP
- General HIPAA, WCAG 2.1 AA, and PCI requirements
- General WordPress content and plugin management
- Project management via JIRA, SmartSheets, Monday.com, and Excel
- Production and workflow management
- Vendor contract review and negotiation
- Team continuous improvement and cost reduction strategies

### **EDUCATION**

BFA in Communication Design, 1998 Kutztown University, Kutztown, PA

